Mystic River Watershed Association Records MS055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- MRWA culture, 1976 -- 1988; 1976 -- 1987; MS055.007; 0.25 Linear Feet
  This series contains items pertinent to the organizational culture of the MRWA that do not fall within more traditional series such as Correspondence or Subject Files. These items include for example, songs and recipes.
  - MRWA song, MS055.007.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - By the gentle flowing mystic, 1980; MS055.007.041.00002; Morrissey, Muriel (Box 41)
    Poem by Muriel Morrissey.
  - Willie Watershed environmental series: book one, 1976; MS055.007.041.00003 (Box 41)
    Signed by author Jack Bowler.
  - Alewife-related recipes, MS055.007.041.00004 (Box 41)
    No Date Avaialable
  - An ecologist's advice regarding courtship, 1988; MS055.007.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - MWRA board of directors, 1987; MS055.007.041.00006 (Box 41)
    Satirical sketches of MRWA board members, presumably by Dr. Herbert Meyer.
- General subject files, 1990 -- 2007; 1991 -- 1997; MS055.008; 3.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 zip file comprising 17 PDFs and 2 ISO files.; 155.7 Megabytes
  This series contains correspondence, reports, legal documents, brochures, newsclippings, and similar documents covering a multitude of geographical entities and scientific topics.
  - Great Meadows notes, 1990 -- 1992; MS055.008.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Birds of the Great Meadows in Lexington, Mass.: a field survey, 1991; MS055.008.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - A citizen's guide to restoring Massachusetts wetlands, 2000; MS055.008.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Toward a watershed approach: a framework for aquatic ecosystem restoration, protection, and management, 1994; MS055.008.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Alewife: a plan for sustainable development, 1993; MS055.008.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resources Authority Combined Sewer Overflow Project, upgrades to existing CSO facilities, supplemental environmental impact report, 1998; MS055.008.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resource Authority Combined Sewer Overflow Project, upgrades to existing CSO facilities, supplemental environmental impact report, 1998; MS055.008.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resource Authority Combined Sewer Overflow Project, upgrades to the Fox Point Treatment Facility, supplemental environmental impact report, 1998; MS055.008.042.00008 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resource Authority Combined Sewer Overflow Project, upgrades to the Fox Point Treatment Facility, supplemental environmental impact report, 1998; MS055.008.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - MassGIS datalayer descriptions and guide to user services, 1997; MS055.008.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - Drainage summary report, Belmont Frontage Road, 2000; MS055.008.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - Environmental assessment/supplemental draft environmental impact report, 1994; MS055.008.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - Environmental assessment/supplemental draft environmental impact report, 1994; MS055.008.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - Final CSO conceptual plan and system master plan part II: CSO strategies, 1994; MS055.008.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - Final CSO conceptual plan and system master plan part II: CSO strategies, 1994; MS055.008.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - The Massachusetts lakes and ponds watershed action strategy, 2001; MS055.008.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - Technical appendix, Cambridge employment, MS055.008.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - ISTEA Transportation Enhancement Program, Cambridge proposal #1: Alewife/Fresh Pond corridor, 1994; MS055.008.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resources Authority: A five-year progress report for the years 1990-1994, MS055.008.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resources Authority, a five-year progress report for the years 1990-1994, executive summary, MS055.008.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Master planning and CSO facility planning, baseline water quality assessment, 1994; MS055.008.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - Final administrative determinations for CSO-impacted waters within the Massachusetts Water Resources Authority sewer service area, 1997; MS055.008.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Water Resources Authority Alewife/Somerville CSO Working Group, 1992; MS055.008.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - Draft first principles of state-wide planning legislation, 1991; MS055.008.042.00024 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts Association of Conservation Commissions annual meeting: no net loss of wetlands, 1991; MS055.008.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Baseline water quality assessment, 1994; MS055.008.042.00026 (Box 42)
  - Baseline water quality assessment, 1994; MS055.008.042.00027 (Box 42)
  - Slide show of the Great Meadows, 1992; MS055.008.042.00028 (Box 42)
  - Birds, 1991 -- 1992; MS055.008.042.00029 (Box 42)
  - Tracking in Great Meadows, 1991 -- 1992; MS055.008.042.00030 (Box 42)
  - Reptiles and amphibians of the Great Meadows, 1993; MS055.008.042.00031 (Box 42)
  - Sewer system, 1993; MS055.008.042.00032 (Box 42)
  - Massachusetts bays 1991 comprehensive conservation and management plan, MS055.008.042.00033 (Box 42)
  - Great Meadows breeding bird survey project, 1991 -- 1992; MS055.008.042.00034 (Box 42)
  - Alewife, 1992 -- 1996; MS055.008.042.00035 (Box 42)
  - Proposed I-93 Woburn interchange, traffic impact study, 1994; MS055.008.042.00036 (Box 42)
  - Proposed I-93 Woburn interchange, air quality and noise impact report, 1994; MS055.008.042.00037 (Box 42)
  - North coastal watershed 1997-1998 water quality assessment report, 2000; MS055.008.042.00038 (Box 42)
  - Environmental notification form for the MWRA Combined Sewer Overflow Project, 1995; MS055.008.042.00039 (Box 42)
  - CSO facilities planning - phase II draft best management practices report, 1996; MS055.008.042.00040 (Box 42)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. I, 1997; MS055.008.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. I, 1997; MS055.008.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vols. II-III, 1997; MS055.008.043.00003 (Box 43)
    First of six folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vols II-III, 1997; MS055.008.043.00004 (Box 43)
    Second of six folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vols II-III, 1997; MS055.008.043.00005 (Box 43)
    Third of six folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vols II-III, 1997; MS055.008.043.00006 (Box 43)
    Fourth of six folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vols II-III, 1997; MS055.008.043.00007 (Box 43)
    Fifth of six folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vols II-III, 1997; MS055.008.043.00008 (Box 43)
    Sixth of six folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, 1997; MS055.008.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, 1997; MS055.008.043.00010 (Box 43)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, 1997; MS055.008.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. V, 1997; MS055.008.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Watershed issues, 1995 -- 1997; MS055.008.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - Somerville development, 1994 -- 1999; MS055.008.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - Proposed retail development/Somerville, final environmental impact report, 1993; MS055.008.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - Final variance for CSO discharges to the Alewife/Upper Mystic Basin, 1999; MS055.008.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - Mystic River Herring workbook, MS055.008.043.00017 (Box 43)
  - Pollution in the Mystic River Basin, 1994; MS055.008.043.00018 (Box 43)
  - The Massachusetts Water Watch Partnership, 1991; MS055.008.043.00019 (Box 43)
  - Integrated watershed management, 1994 -- 1996; MS055.008.043.00020 (Box 43)
  - Environmental notification form, Mugar Parcel, Arlington, Mass., 2000; MS055.008.043.00021 (Box 43)
  - MWRA CSO Project, upgrades to existing CSO facilities, Notice of project change, 1997; MS055.008.043.00022 (Box 43)
  - Final report: measurements and loadings of polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons in storm water, CSOs, rivers, and publicly owned treatment works discharging to Massachusetts bays, 1995; MS055.008.043.00023 (Box 43)
  - A report upon the alewife fisheries of Massachusetts, MS055.008.043.00024 (Box 43)
  - Weeds, 1992 -- 1997; MS055.008.043.00025 (Box 43)
  - Fishways, 1993 -- 1999; MS055.008.043.00026 (Box 43)
  - An Alewife area ecology guide, 1994; MS055.008.043.00027 (Box 43)
  - Meadow Brook Park and Mill Brook, 1994; MS055.008.043.00028 (Box 43)
  - Blair Pond master plan, 1999; MS055.008.043.00029 (Box 43)
  - Eutrophication and aquatic plant management in Massachusetts, generic environmental impact report, executive summary and table of contents, 1997; MS055.008.043.00030 (Box 43)
  - Draft construction impact guidelines for phase I waiver CSO Projects, 1998; MS055.008.043.00031 (Box 43)
  - Draft transportation improvement program, 1993-1995, 1992; MS055.008.043.00032 (Box 43)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plans and environmental impact report, vol. VII, 1991 -- 2000; MS055.008.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. VII, 1996; MS055.008.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Draft combined sewer overflow facilities plan and environmental impact report, vol. VII, 1996; MS055.008.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Transportation, 1991 -- 1994; MS055.008.044.00004 (Box 44)
  - Proposed highway construction projects, 1993; MS055.008.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - Environmental assessment final environmental impact report: proposed I-93 Woburn interchange, 1995; MS055.008.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - Environmental assessment final environmental impact report: proposed I-93 Woburn interchange, 1995; MS055.008.045.00001 (Box 45)
  - MWRA CSO and master planning program, draft recommended plan: East Boston and Chelsea, 1994; MS055.008.045.00002 (Box 45)
  - MRWA CSO and master planning program, draft recommended plan: Alewife Brook and Mystic River, 1994; MS055.008.045.00003 (Box 45)
  - Coastal nonpoint pollution control plan, 1995; MS055.008.045.00004 (Box 45)
  - MWRA CSO Project, upgrades to existing facilities, supplemental environmental impact report, 1998; MS055.008.045.00005 (Box 45)
  - MRWA CSO Project, upgrades to existing CSO facilities, supplemental environmental impact report, 1998; MS055.008.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - Bird surveys, 1992; MS055.008.045.00007 (Box 45)
  - MIT Mystic Research, 2007; MS055.008.00001; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 zip file comprising 17 PDFs and 2 ISO files.; 155.7 Megabytes
    Closed due to copyright.
    This digital object contains files from two CD-ROM discs in Anne Sauer's office related to MIT Mystic Research.
- Additional accessions, 1980 -- 2005; MS055.009
  - Maps, 1980 -- 2005; MS055-001 (Box data_value_missing_b74612d04a18e0064b53e841ccb46e7e, Box 1)
    Materials found in DCA storage room. Accession information is unknown. Materials are oversized and need preservation. Dates are approximate.
  - Maps, 1980 -- 2005; MS055-002 (Box data_value_missing_6c5a2d4c1c410d41561eab7fdd5230ef, Box 2)
    Materials found in DCA storage room. Accession information is unknown. Materials are oversized and need preservation. Dates are approximate.; former barcode 39090015515980g
  - Maps, 1980 -- 2005; MS055-003 (Box data_value_missing_4542bc7adb822f3e07e5f2e78702f6b5, Box 3)